Wolf, Benjamin H. Additional Arbitration Files 5539
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  10/22/74. S-153-74. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Assignment to Work Outside Unit.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  10/22/74. M-402-72. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue--Layoff- Seniority--Bumping.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  10/22/74. M-388-73. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Assignment to Work Outside Area.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  10/22/74. M-1820-74. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Demotion--Seniority.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  12/30/74. M-1984-74. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Contracting Out--Past Practice.
- American Airlines vs. Air Line Stewards and Stewardesses Association, Local 550, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  2/6/76. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, Supporting Documents. Issue: Fringe Benefits--Meal Allowance.
- Miscellaneous American Airline (Box 41, Folder 4-end)
  Transcripts, correspondence, dispositions, submissions and other related documents re. various cases.
- Arrow Shirt Company vs. Amalgamated Clothing and Textiles Workers Union, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  12/13/71. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay; Assignment of Jobs.
- Associated Press vs. Newspaper Guild, Wire Service Guild, Local 222, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 2-end)
  8/22/75. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Legal Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Disloyalty--Improper Job Attitude.
- Brooklyn Union Gas Company vs. Transport Workers Union, Local 101, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  4/24/70. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Tardiness; Improper Personal Conduct--Offensive Language--Insubordination
- Enro Shirt Company vs. Amalgamated Clothing Workers, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  3/21/72. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Layoff--Transfers--Rate of pay; Discrimination.
- Manhattan Industries vs. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  11/13/71. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Strikes--Work Stoppages
- New York City Police Department vs. Patrolmen's Benevolent Association, 1975-1976 (Box 43, Folder 4-end)
  RC, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents, Exhibits. Issue: Schedules of Work--Shift Scheduling--Change of Schedules
- New York City Police Department vs. Patrolmen's Benevolent Association, 1975-1976 (Box 44)
- Northwest Airlines vs. Air Line Pilots Association, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1-8)
  1/2/76. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Transcripts, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Recall--Method of Recall.
- Publix Shirt Corporation vs. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union of America, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  2/6/73. Routine Correspondence. Issue: Transfers- -Rates of Pay.
- Miscellaneous unidentified documentation re. case files (Box 45, Folder 10-end)